AHMED ELBLASY STUDIO MANAGER

R E S U M E



AHMED ELBLASY

Hi, my name is Ahmed Elblasy, I'm a studio manager. I have worked within most areas of design from sketching, 2D designing, 3D modeling, branding, web, mobile apps, prints, photography, handcraft to full supervision of manufacturing processes with more than 13 years of work experience and continuous learning.

EXPERIENCE

STUDIO MANAGER

Influence Communications
EVENT MANAGEMENT

Oct 2019 - Present

Design Responsibilities

Coming up with an art direction that suits the client and what he intends from his event and coordinating with the 2D, 3D and animation team members while supervising the design process.

Management Responsibilities

Receiving tasks, distributing them to the team, and organizing delivery dates in a way that ensures the team's comfort and excellent work output.

HEAD OF DESIGN

AWstreams
DIGITAL / SOCIAL MEDIA

Dec 2017 - Sep 2019

Design Responsibilities

Designing templates that suit the clients' identity and supervising the quality of the 2D and animated designs produced using my templates.

Management Responsibilities

Divide social media calendasr with the help of the client management team then distributing them to the design team, organizing delivery dates and excellent work output.

ART DIRECTOR

Star Unlimited GRAPHIC DESIGN / PRODUCTION HOUSE

Apr 2013 - Nov 2017

Design Responsibilities

Working on designs for publications and the decorations of retail window displays.

Management Responsibilities

Distributing tasks between members of the design team and supervising the printing, implementation and installation processes of the work, this includes display stands, screens and lighting.

PART TIME ARCHITECT

Karawia Construction

Nov 2008 - Mar 2013

Design Responsibilities

Reviewing the architectural drawings and sometimes amending them in proportion to the budget of the project.

PART TIME ARCHITECT

Universal Consulting

Dec 2007 - Mar 2013

Design Responsibilities

CAD drawing the architectural designs for facades, cross sectors, and floor plans, in addition to modeling and rendering 3D shots for the projects.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Graphic Home GRAPHIC DESIGN

Oct 2006 - Nov 2007

Design Responsibilities

Implementing 2D, 3D designs and animating some basic videos.

VISUALIZER AND MODELER

Lotus Engineering Consulting ARCHITECTUR DESIGN

Jan 2004 - Sep 2006

Design Responsibilities

CAD drawing the architectural designs for facades, cross sectors, and floor plans, in addition to modeling and rendering 3D shots for the projects.

PHOTOGRAPHER AND RETOUCHER

Oscar Studio

Jan 2003 - Dec 2003

Design Responsibilities

Digital photography and photo editing.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURE

Suez Canal University 2004 - 2008

HIGH SCHOOL

Canal Secondary School 2001 - 2003

SKILLS

3D	UI and UX	Photo Manipulation
HTML and CSS	Photography	CAD
VFX	Video Editing	Illustration
Drawing	Game Making	

NEXT STEPS

Apply for a master in architecture design.	Join the School of Arabic Calligraphy.	Study more about video games and cartoon industries.
Become a professional photographer.	Improve my skills in digital painting.	Improve my visual effects skills.

Make a short movie using the stop motion technique.

CLOUD OF INTERESTS

chess origami basketball space sketching technology youtube writing music fashion white vfx photoshop reading math running photography magic architecture pixar time swimming internet design shooting environment english physics shells diy computers drawing history geology blue anime movies astrology beach comics egyptology disney black moon games furniture sky